{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"738/9",
			"answer":"738/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"774/9",
			"answer":"774/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"904/2",
			"answer":"904/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"656/8",
			"answer":"656/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"912/3",
			"answer":"912/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"585/3",
			"answer":"585/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"504/8",
			"answer":"504/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"568/8",
			"answer":"568/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"144/6",
			"answer":"144/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"872/8",
			"answer":"872/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"105/7",
			"answer":"105/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"904/4",
			"answer":"904/4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"489/3",
			"answer":"489/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"639/3",
			"answer":"639/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"984/6",
			"answer":"984/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"426/3",
			"answer":"426/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"795/5",
			"answer":"795/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"264/6",
			"answer":"264/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"925/5",
			"answer":"925/5",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"680/2",
			"answer":"680/2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"30/3",
			"answer":"30/3",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"80/8",
			"answer":"80/8",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},
		
		{
			"Problem":"49/7",
			"answer":"49/7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"81/9",
			"answer":"81/9",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"36/6",
			"answer":"36/6",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}